Guide to the Robert Steck Papers ALBA.104
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Prisoners of the Good Fight
  - Subseries II:B: Subject Files
    - Correspondence: Carl Geiser w/ Max Shufer, undated, Sep 1978-Mar 1990 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence: Carl Geiser w/ others, undated, May 1977-Mar 1995 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence: Carl Geiser w/Robert Steck, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Carl Geiser w/Robert Steck, Jan 1976-Oct 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Carl Geiser w/Robert Steck, Nov 1980-Feb 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Carl Geiser w/Robert Steck, Mar 1983-Jul 1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Carl Geiser w/Robert Steck, Aug 1985-Feb 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: General, undated, Apr 1978-Nov 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Giler, Henry, undated, Jun 1980-Mar 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Shapiro, Linn, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Cultural Life in a Concentration Camp": Mavard, Morgan (copy), Jan 1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Dust Jacket, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Service of the U.S.A.: "The Right of American Citizens Imprisoned by the Spanish Insurgent Military Forces to Diplomatic Interposition on Their Behalf", 1940 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, Dec 1937-May 1939 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Fundraising: Grants, undated, Apr 1979-Jul 1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising: for Research and Writing, undated, Jan 1980-Dec 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Fundraising: Ring Lardner, Jr., undated, Jan 1980-Feb 1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - German and Czech Prisoners, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Great Britain: Foreign Office (list of documents), undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Greeting Card from Zaragoza Inmate, ca.1938 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Hellman, Lillian: on Carney Visit to San Pedro de Cardena (article), Jul 1938 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Italian Involvement, undated, 1937-1938, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Jaily News": on Carney Visit to San Pedro de Cardena (no. 15, p. 2, partial photocopy), Aug 11, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Existence and Location of Originals
      Original handwritten issue of "Jaily News" in Abraham Lincoln Brigade Vertical Files: Subjects (ALBA.VF.001), Tamiment Library.
    - Lists of POW Names and Contacts, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Manuscript: Draft Pages, undated, Dec 1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Martin, Fredericka, undated, May 1979-Mar 1980 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Orders and Reader Responses, undated, Nov 1986-Mar 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Publication: Editorial Process, Dec 1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Publication: Frances Goldin, Literary Agent, undated, Aug 1979-May 1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Publication: General, Mar 1980-Jul 1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Publication: Lawrence Hill Publishers, Oct 1980-Jun 1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Publication: Rejections, Dec 1979-May 1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Publication: Statements of Support for, Mar 1980 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Questionnaire re: POWs, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Red Cross: American and International (correspondence with Geiser, Steck, and others), Jan 1939-Aug 1939 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Reports re: Prisoners, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Research and Notes: I, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Research and Notes: II, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Research and Notes: III, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Research: Requests for Information re: Prisoners, undated, Jul 1980 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Review Queries and Mailing Lists, undated, Oct 1986-Jun 1987 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Reviews and Recommendations, undated, Jan 1987-Oct 1987 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Sales, Promotion and Distribution, undated, Jan 1980-Jul 1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Service, Elman, undated, Feb 1980-Jul 1987 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Spanish Ex-Servicemen's Association (London): "Franco's Prisoners Speak" (pamphlet), Dec 1960 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Spanish Fascist Oath (photocopy), Sep 1936 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - U.S. Embassy: Crain, Earl T., undated, May 1939-Jun 1940, Nov 1979-Jan 1980 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - U.S. Embassy and Foreign Service, May 1939 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - VALB: Prisoner Historical Committee, undated, Jul 1981-Mar 1995 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Work Plans and Proposals, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)